Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 97, Folder: 13 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: your hydro health plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: your hydro pension fund, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: your hydro pension fund, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: your long term disability plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Extended Health benefits for Ontario Hydro, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: The Union Clerical - Technical Job Evaluation Manual, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: Your Employee Information Report, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: Wind power, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: Thunder Bay Generating Station Extension, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Pickering Generating Station, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: Radiation Control, Publication (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Box: 97, Folder: 14 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Corporate Reputations, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
    By Opinion Research Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Memorandum re Governmant Regulation of Business: The New Outlook, the New Reality, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Survey results on inflation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: An International Network of Companies, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Public Opinion Index Special Report, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Market Insights, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Interpreting the Company through the Employee Publication, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: Industry's Communications System, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: News from Opinion Research Corporation, Publication (Box 97, Folder 14)
- Box: 97, Folder: 15 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Organization of American Employers' Association, Inc., Publication (Box 97, Folder 15)
    By American Employers' Association, Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 16 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Resources Counselors, Inc. v.1:no.1 (1969:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Resources Counselors, Inc. v.1:no.2 (1969:May). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Resources Counselors, Inc. v.1:no.3 (1969:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Resources Counselors, Inc. v.1:no.4 (1970:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.2:no.1 (1970:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.2:no.2 (1970:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 7: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.2:no.3 (1971:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.2:no.4 (1970:May). Actually May 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.3:no.1 (1971:Aug.). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.3:no.2 (1972:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: irconcepts, Publication (Box 97, Folder 16)
    By Organization Resources Counselors, Inc. v.4:no.1 (1973:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 17 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Thank you for your inquiry, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
    By Charles R. Dillon. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: OPMA Activates for 1978, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
    By Modern Office Procedures. February, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Concepts: Organization Spans of Control (Part 1), Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
    By Charles R. Dillon. v.1:no.4 (1978). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Management Concepts: Managerial Productivity What Is Wrong?, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Newsletter, Publication (Box 97, Folder 17)
    By OPMA (Organization Planning Management Association). Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 18 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Selection and Development of Supervision, Publication (Box 97, Folder 18)
    By Outboard, Marine and Manufacturing Co., Inc. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 19 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Training, Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
    By E. R. Summerhayes. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Job Rating, Publication (Box 97, Folder 19)
    By Otis Elevator Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 20 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Group Insurance lan for Employees, Publication (Box 97, Folder 20)
    By S.E. Overton Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 21 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Newark Yarns, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation. v.22:no.10 (1961:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Newark Yarns, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation. v.23:no.3 (1962:Mar.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Newark Yarns, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation. v.23:no.4 (1962:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Step Ahead through the Education Refund Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas. April 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Retirement Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas. March 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Owens-Corning is Fiberglas, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas. July 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Discover the Future of Fiberglas, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas. January 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Invention Award Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
    By Owens-Corning Fiberglas. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Travel Accident Policy Provisions, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Voluntary Group Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Timetable of Employee Benefits for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Owens-Corning Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Savings and Stock Investment Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: The Trial of Freedom, Publication (Box 97, Folder 21)
- Box: 97, Folder: 22 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Personnel Program, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    By Owens-Illinois Glass. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance in Owens-Illinois, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: O-I Outlook, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    By Owens-Illinois Glass. no.194 (1975:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Owens-Illinois Glass Company: Its Past, Its Products, and Its People, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Sone Interview Reactions to Four Advanced Management Training Programs, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    By John H. Rapparlie. General Industrial Relations Division Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Management Inventory, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    By Harold Mayfield. General Industrial Relations Division Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: An Interview Study of Some Opinions on Retirement by Selected Groups of Company People, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: The Issue of the Annual Wage, Publication (Box 97, Folder 22)
    By M. M. Olander. Presented before the American Chemists' Association, New York, NY, November 24, 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 23 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Winning Plans in the Pabst Postwar Employment Awards, Publication (Box 97, Folder 23)
    By Pabst Brewing Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Winning Plans in the Pabst Postwar Employment Awards, Publication (Box 97, Folder 23)
    By Pabst Brewing Company. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 24 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Recommendations for Safety Rules for Stevedoring Operations Aboard Ship, Publication (Box 97, Folder 24)
    By Waterfront Employers' Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pacific Coast Marine Safety Code: Stevedoring Operations on Board Ship, Publication (Box 97, Folder 24)
    By Pacific American Steamship Association. Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 25 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: PG&E Energy Control Center, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Sun Energy: A Guide to Solar Heating Equipment, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Radiation and Nuclear Power Plants, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Morro Bay, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: The Young Sound of PG & E, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Conservation Tips from PG & E: Cooling Your Home More Efficiently, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: The Meter Minders' Guidebook: 67 Ways to Conserve Energy, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Pacific Service Employers Credit Union, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Put Yourself in the Engineering Picture, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Think About Joining the Professionals at PG & E, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Mighty Moss, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: The Geysers, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Nuclear Power at Humboldt Bay, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: Employment Manual, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 15: Your Career Your Company Your P.S.E.A., Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 16: Insulate. Save energy., Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Electric and Gas Industries Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Company Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 18: Your Job and Your Company, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 19: A Career: Your future may be here, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 20: PG & E Diablo Canyon Nuclear Information Center, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 21: Career Opportunities at PG & E, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 22: PE&G Life, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. v.21:no.1 (1978:Jan.). Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Outlook '78, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 24: Procedure Concerning Proposed Disciplinary Actions to be Taken Against Protected Class Employees, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Carl F. Poteet. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Summary of Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 26: PG & E Organization Chart, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 27: PE&G Life, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. v.21:no.4 (1978:May. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: PE&G Life, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. v.20:no.2 (1977:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 29: PE&G Life, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. v.20:no.7 (1977:Sep.). Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Engineering Your Career, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 31: Standard Wage and Salary Ranges on 40-Hour Week Basis, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Item 32: PE&G Life, Publication (Box 97, Folder 25)
    By Pacific Gas and Electric. v.18:no.10 (1975:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
- Box: 97, Folder: 26 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Employee Benefits and Summary of Benefits, Publication (Box 97, Folder 26)
- Box: 97, Folder: 27 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Performance Review/ Promotion System: A Supervisor's Handbook, Publication (Box 97, Folder 27)
- Box: 98, Folder: 1 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement and Consolidation of Pacific Maritime Association, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. December. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working Penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. June 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Table of Long shore Hourly Wage Rates When Working Penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. October 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. November 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. December 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. January 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. February 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. March 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. April 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. May 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. June 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. July 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. August 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. September 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. October 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. November 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. August. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. September. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. October. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. November. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. January. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. February 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. March. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. April. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. May. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 40: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 41: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 42: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. February. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 44: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 45: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 46: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. June. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 48: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 49: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 50: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 51: Monthly Research bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 52: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 53: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 54: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 55: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 56: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 57: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 58: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 59: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 60: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 61: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 62: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 63: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 64: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 65: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 66: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 67: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 68: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 69: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 70: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 71: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. June-July. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 73: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 74: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. September-October. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Item 76: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Box: 98, Folder: 2 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: here's health to west coast seafarers, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Outline of ILWU-PMA Benefit Funds, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. Welfare & Retirement Plans. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working Penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working Penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Overtime and Penalty Earnings of Seamen, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. September 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Seamen's Earnings Under Pacific Coast Contracts 1953, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. August 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Costs: Vessel Operations under Pacific Coast Controls, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Pacific Maritime Association. December 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: By-Laws as Amended of Pacific Maritime Association, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: By-Laws, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: St. Sure Resigns PMA Post, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Rocco C. Siciliano, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: By Laws, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Benefits Provided Stewards Department Employees on PMA Ships Regardless of Union Affiliation or Activity, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
    By Welfare Fund. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working Penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Table of Longshore Hourly Wage Rates When Working penalty Hours and Penalty Cargo, Publication (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Box: 98, Folder: 3 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Safety Code, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
    By Pacific Coast Marine. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: By Laws, Amended, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Year End Report of Pacific Coast Shipping, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: ECA and American Shipping, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Year End Report on West Coast Shipping`, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Story of a Strike, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Pacific Coast Longshoreman, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining in the Pacific Coast Maritime Industry, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Overtime on Overtime, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Pacific Maritime Association, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Pacific Coast Maritime Report, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The Deck Officer of The American Merchant Marine, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The Licensed Engineer of The American merchant Marine, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: The Steward's Department, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: The Sailor on West Coast Ships, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: The Unlicensed Men of the Engine Room, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: The Pacific American Shipowners Association and the Men Who Sail the Ships, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: The Accident Prevention Bureau, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: American Pacific Trade Routes, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: The Pacific Coast Maritime Wage Picture, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Domestic Water Transportation's Case Against Depressed Competitive Rail Rates, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Monthly Research Bulletin, Publication (Box 98, Folder 3)